Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - M
        - MAW - Ekabo | Elements of life (unreleased mixes), 2000; SR-17806; MAW; Vega, Little Louie (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17807. 2 copies.
        - MAW - Ekabo | Elements of life (unreleased mixes), 2000; SR-17807; MAW; Vega, Little Louie (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17806. 2 copies.
        - MAW - Ekabo | Elements of life (unreleased mixes), 2000; SR-17808; MAW; Vega, Little Louie (Box 350)
        - MAW - Ékabo, 2000; SR-17809; MAW (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17810. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MAW-046; A-side Matrix # MAW 046 A
        - MAW - Ékabo, 2000; SR-17810; MAW (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17809. 2 copies.
        - Max & Sam - Young man rumble, 1994; SR-17811; Max & Sam (Box 350)
          Catalog # 44 77427; A-side Matrix # XSS-77427-A2
          Ruffhouse Records
        - Max, Trey - Renegade bass supersonic volume 1, 1994; SR-17812; Max, Trey (Box 350)
          Catalog # FREEZE LP 55050; A-side Matrix # MR-55050-A
          Freeze Records
        - Max, Trey - Renegade bass supersonic volume 2, 1995; SR-17813; Max, Trey (Box 350)
          Catalog # FREEZE 55051; A-side Matrix # MR-55051-A
        - Max, Willie - I'm not your girlfriend, 1999; SR-17814; Max, Willie (Box 350)
          Catalog # U8P-1472; A-side Matrix # U8P-1472-A
        - Max, Willie - Can't get enough, 1998; SR-17815; Max, Willie (Box 350)
          Catalog # 374633038-1; A-side Matrix # 374633038-1A
        - Maxmimum Hype - It was a dream!; Something from the kizzo!, 1995; SR-17816; Maxmimum Hype (Box 350)
          Catalog # MH110010; A-side Matrix # MH-110010-A
          Pure D Flava Records
        - Maximum Style - Admit to love (disc one), 1996; SR-17817; Maximum Style (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17818. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MAX 2 - A
          Parousia
        - Maximum Style - Admit to love (disc two), 1996; SR-17818; Maximum Style (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17817. Double album.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MAX 2 - C2
        - Maxim - Carmen Queasy, 2000; SR-17819; Maxim (Box 350)
          Catalog # XLT 119; A-side Matrix # XLT 119 A1
          XL Recordings
        - Maximus III - Rock it out, 1982; SR-17820; Maximus III (Box 350)
          Catalog # CS 2020; A-side Matrix # SC 2020 A
          Express Records
        - Maxwell - Till the cops come knockin' the opus, 1996; SR-17821; Maxwell (Box 350)
          Catalog # 44 78275; A-side Matrix # XSS-78275-A
        - Maxwell - Ascension don't ever wonder the tribute, 1996; SR-17822; Maxwell (Box 350)
          Catalog # XSS 78365; A-side Matrix # XSS-782365-A
        - Maxwell - Luxury: cococure, 1998; SR-17823; Maxwell (Box 350)
          Catalog # CAS 4173; A-side Matrix # XSS-4173-A-1
        - Maxwell - Maxwell's urban hang suite, 1995; SR-17824; Maxwell (Box 350)
          Catalog # CAS 7505; A-side Matrix # XSS7505A-1A
        - Mayana - Skips a beat, 1983; SR-17825; Mayana (Box 350)
          Catalog # DMD 681; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-45484-1
        - Members of Mayday - Soundtropolis, 1999; SR-17826; Members of Mayday (Box 350)
          Catalog # 74321 65650 1; A-side Matrix # B921036-01-A1 MK
        - Mayday - Life in space, 1981; SR-17827; Mayday (Box 350)
          Catalog # SP-17180; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-017180-A-CT2
        - Mayday - The day x, 1996; SR-17828; Mayday (Box 350)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 45 UPM
        - Mayers, Nappy - Celebration time, 1981; SR-17829; Mayers, Nappy (Box 350)
          Catalog # NCR 475; A-side Matrix # NCR-475-A
          Charlie's Records
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Live in Europe (disc one), 1988; SR-17830; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17831. Double album.
          Catalog # CUR-2-2901; A-side Matrix # CUR-2901-A
          Curtom Records
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Live in Europe (disc two), 1988; SR-17831; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 350)
          In same jacket as # SR-17830. Double album.
          Catalog # CUR-2-2901; A-side Matrix # CUR-2901C
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Toot an'toot an'toot; She don't let nobody (but me), 1981; SR-17832; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 350)
          Catalog # NBS-008; A-side Matrix # NBS-AL-008 GD
          The Boardwalk Entertainment Co
        - Mayfield, Curtis - No one knows about a good thing (you don't have to cry), 1996; SR-17833; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 350)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8618; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8618-1-A-SR1
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Got to be real; On and on, SR-17834; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 350)
          Catalog # 12-PO52; A-side Matrix # 12-PO52-A
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Curtis, 1995; SR-17835; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 350)
          Catalog # CPLP 8036; A-side Matrix # CPLP8036A
          Charly Groove
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Curtis, 1995; SR-17836; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 351)
          Catalog # CRS-8005; A-side Matrix # 5032 CRS 8005-1
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Superfly, 1994; SR-17837; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 351)
          Catalog # CPLP 8039; A-side Matrix # CPLP8039A1
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Superfly, 1972; SR-17838; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 351)
          Catalog # RS-1-3046; A-side Matrix # RS-1-3046-AS-KL 1
        - Mazarati - Player's ball, 1986; SR-17844; Mazarati (Box 351)
          Catalog # 0-20438; A-side Matrix # 0 B-22662-SH1
          Paisley Park
        - Mazarati - 100 MPH, 1985; SR-17845; Mazarati (Box 351)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2392; A-side Matrix # PTO-A1-2393-RE-1-SA1
        - Mazarati - Stroke, 1986; SR-17846; Mazarati (Box 351)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2546; A-side Matrix # OB-25254-SH1
        - Mazarati - 100 MPH, 1985; SR-17847; Mazarati (Box 351)
        - Mazarati - The jungle dub experience, 1995; SR-17848; Mazarati (Box 351)
          Catalog # ARILP 109; A-side Matrix # ARILP109-1
          Ariwa
        - Mazda, Richard - Hands of fate, 1983; SR-17849; Mazda, Richard (Box 351)
          Catalog # SP-70034; A-side Matrix # SPO-70034-A-ES 1
          I.R.S. Records
        - Maze - I wanna be with you, 1986; SR-17850; Maze; Beverly, Frankie (Box 351)
          Catalog # SPRO-9750; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9750-100359
        - Maze - Laid back girl, 1993; SR-17851; Maze; Beverly, Frankie (Box 351)
          Catalog # PRO-A-6566; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-6566-SR1
        - Maze - Back to basics (disc one), 1993; SR-17852; Maze; Beverly, Frankie (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17853. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-6603; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-6603-SR1
        - Maze - Back to basics (disc two), 1993; SR-17853; Maze; Beverly, Frankie (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17852. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-6603; A-side Matrix # PRO-A3-6603-SR1
        - Maze - Southern girl; I want to thank you, 1980; SR-17854; Maze; Beverly, Frankie (Box 351)
          Catalog # SPRO-9449; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9449 G-1
        - Maze - Live in Los Angeles, 1986; SR-17855; Maze; Beverly, Frankie (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17856. Double album.
          Catalog # SWBB-12479; A-side Matrix # O B-24936-F2
        - Maze - Live in Los Angeles, 1986; SR-17856; Maze; Beverly, Frankie (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17855. Double album.
          Catalog # SWBB-12479; A-side Matrix # O B-24938-F2
        - Mazi - North & Damen (get up) (part 2 of 2), 1999; SR-17857; Mazi; Mikkhiel (Box 351)
          Catalog # MBD-012; A-side Matrix # MBD-021-80
          Morbido Records
          Barcelona, Spain
        - M.B. Industry - Searching, 1999; SR-17858; M.B. Industry (Box 351)
          Catalog # TB 394; A-side Matrix # TB 394 A
        - MC 900 ft Jesus - If I only had a brain, 1994; SR-17859; MC 900 ft Jesus (Box 351)
          Catalog # 0-41554; A-side Matrix # 0-41554-A
          American Recordings
        - MC ADE - Da' train, 1989; SR-17860; MC ADE (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17861. Different discs.
          Catalog # FS-5634; A-side Matrix # FS-5634-A
          4 Sight Records
          Fort Lauderdale, Florida
        - Afrika Bambaataa - Planet rock, 1982; SR-17861; Afrika Bambaataa; Soul Sonic Force; Planet Patrol (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17860. Different discs.
          Catalog # TB 823; A-side Matrix # TB-823-A
        - MC Andinho |MC Rodrigo |Melodia, Haroldo - Ilha do governador | Paz e amor, 1995; SR-17862; MC Andinho; MC Rodrigo; Melodia, Haroldo; MC Junior; MC Leonardo; Gera (Box 351)
          Catalog # 443.082; A-side Matrix # 443082 A
        - MC and his Great Googa-Moogas - Keep your shoes on! (say yeah), 1982; SR-17863; MC and his Great Googa-Moogas (Box 351)
          Catalog # 12EMI 5302; A-side Matrix # 12 EMI 5302 A-1-1-1
          EMI
        - MC Bam Bam - It's all about me, 1990; SR-17864; MC Bam Bam (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17865. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PW 458; A-side Matrix # PW-458 A
          Pow Wow Records
        - MC Bam Bam - It's all about me, 1990; SR-17865; MC Bam Bam (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17864. 2 copies.
        - MC Bam Bam - Wind me up, 1988; SR-17866; MC Bam Bam (Box 351)
          Catalog # PW 436; A-side Matrix # PW 436-A
        - MC Batata - Feira de acari; Conselho, 1990; SR-17867; MC Batata (Box 351)
          Catalog # 2801 447; A-side Matrix # 2801447
        - MC Bira - A massa do Sao Carlos; Rap samba da mangueira, 1995; SR-17868; MC Bira; MR Catra (Box 351)
          Catalog # 443.081; A-side Matrix # 443081 A
        - MC Bira - A massa do sao carlos; Rap samba da mangueira, 1995; SR-17869; MC Bira; MR Catra (Box 351)
        - MC Breed - Big baller, 1995; SR-17870; MC Breed (Box 351)
          Catalog # WRA 8148-1; A-side Matrix # WRA-8148-A-RE-1
          Wrap Records
        - MC Breed - Big baller, 1995; SR-17871; MC Breed (Box 351)
        - MC Chill - Nightmare on chill street; Nothing can save you now, 1987; SR-17872; MC Chill (Box 351)
          Catalog # SF 817; A-side Matrix # SF-817-A
          Fever Records
          Yonkers, New York
        - MC Classy Rick - We can make you dance; Drop the bass, 1988; SR-17873; MC Classy Rick (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17874. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TH-004; A-side Matrix # TH-004-A
          Turf Handler
        - MC Classy Rick - We can make you dance; Drop the bass, 1988; SR-17874; MC Classy Rick (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17873. 2 copies.
        - MC Claudinho | MC Buchecha | de Pilares, Carlinhos - Bate bum bum; Gira roda, 1995; SR-17875; MC Claudinho; MC Buchecha; de Pilares, Carlinhos; MC Markynhos; MC Dollores; MC Marron (Box 351)
          Catalog # 443.08; A-side Matrix # 443080 A
        - MC Cool Rock & M.C. Chaszy Chess - Boot the booty, 1988; SR-17876; MC Cool Rock & M.C. Chaszy Chess (Box 351)
          Catalog # VR 1204; A-side Matrix # 1204-A
          North Miami, Florida
        - MC Dollar Bill - Lifestyles of the fresh and fly, 1986; SR-17877; MC Dollar Bill (Box 351)
          Catalog # PRO-7104; A-side Matrix # PRO-7104-A
        - MC Don & E.Z. Ed - Party rocker; Beware of the beat, 1988; SR-17878; MC Don & E.Z. Ed (Box 351)
          Catalog # PAL-7213; A-side Matrix # PAL-7213A
          Zakia Records
        - MC Dr. "T" - I don't want to be late!, 1986; SR-17879; MC Dr. "T" (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17880. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DTT 142; A-side Matrix # DT 142A
          Dr. "T" Tunes
          Oakland Gardens, New York
        - MC Dr. "T" - I don't want to be late!, 1986; SR-17880; MC Dr. "T" (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17879. 2 copies.
        - MC Eiht - Goin' out like geez, 1994; SR-17881; MC Eiht; CMW (Box 351)
          Catalog # AED 6758; A-side Matrix # XSS 6758A -1A
          Epic Street
        - MC Eiht - Thicker than water, 1999; SR-17882; MC Eiht (Box 351)
          Catalog # SPRO 81284; A-side Matrix # 81284-13-A
        - MC Eric Aka Me One - Before we get started, SR-17883; MC Eric Aka Me One (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17884. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # MEONE 1; A-side Matrix # ME ONE 1 A-1U-1
          MC Eric
        - MC Eric Aka Me One - Before we get started, SR-17884; MC Eric Aka Me One (Box 351)
          In same jacket as # SR-17883. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - MC Fresh C - My brougham, 1988; SR-17885; MC Fresh C (Box 351)
          Catalog # HAL 12104; A-side Matrix # HAL-12104-A
          Boomtown Records
        - MC Nem | MC ET - Funk e bom demais | Rap do contexto, 1995; SR-17886; MC Nem; MC ET; MC Leandro; MC Alvinho (Box 351)
          Catalog # 443.044; A-side Matrix # 443044 A
        - MC Hammer - Turn this mutha out; Ring 'em, 1988; SR-17887; MC Hammer (Box 351)
          Catalog # V-15437; A-side Matrix # V-1-15437-Z2
        - MC Hammer - Sultry funk, 1995; SR-17888; MC Hammer (Box 351)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7544; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7544-A-SR1
          Giant Records
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - MC Hammer - Pray (remix), 1990; SR-17889; MC Hammer (Box 351)
          Catalog # SPRO-79463; A-side Matrix # SPRO-79463-Z1
        - MC Jeffox - Super spurm, 1990; SR-17890; MC Jeffox (Box 351)
          Catalog # T.G. 101; A-side Matrix # TG-101-A
          Taste Good Records
        - MC Juice - Living a white lie, 1989; SR-17891; MC Juice (Box 351)
          Catalog # PNT 009; A-side Matrix # PNT-009-A-2
          Production House
        - MC Junior - Rap do abc II; De baile em baile, 1995; SR-17892; MC Junior; MC Leonardo (Box 351)
          Catalog # 51.681; A-side Matrix # 51681 A
          Sony Music Entertainment
        - MC Junior - Rap do centenario; Rap das armas, 1995; SR-17893; MC Junior; MC Leonardo (Box 351)
          Catalog # 51.678; A-side Matrix # 51678 A
        - MC Junior - Rap dos raps; Rainha rocinha, 1995; SR-17894; MC Junior; MC Leonardo (Box 351)
          Catalog # 51.679; A-side Matrix # 51679 A
        - MC Junior - Se liga; De baile em baile, 1995; SR-17895; MC Junior; MC Leonardo (Box 351)
          Catalog # 51.68; A-side Matrix # 51680 A
        - MC La Kim - We got the funk, 1988; SR-17896; MC La Kim (Box 351)
          Catalog # TUF 128031; A-side Matrix # TUF-128031-A
        - MC Leu | MC Dinho - Casual, a mais balancante do Rio, 1995; SR-17897; MC Leu; MC Dinho; MC Naldinho; MC Renato (Box 351)
          Catalog # 443.065; A-side Matrix # 443065 A
        - MC Luscious - Lollypop, 1994; SR-17898; MC Luscious (Box 351)
          Catalog # BDR4443; A-side Matrix # S-29870
          Bandit Records
          Pembroke Pines, Florida
        - MC Lyte - Lyte as a rock, 1988; SR-17899; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          Catalog # 0-96596; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-56248-56249-1
          Firsty Priority Records
        - MC Lyte - Everyday, 1996; SR-17900; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          Catalog # ED-5863; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5863-A1
          Eastwest Records
        - MC Lyte - I can't make a mistake, 1998; SR-17901; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          Catalog # ED-6092; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6092A-1
        - MC Lyte - Seven & seven (disc one), 1998; SR-17902; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17903. Double album.
          Catalog # ED-6096; A-side Matrix # ST-EW-981421-A
        - MC Lyte - Seven & seven (disc two), 1998; SR-17903; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17902. Double album.
        - MC Lyte - Cold rock a party, 1996; SR-17904; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          Catalog # ED-5890; A-side Matrix # ED-5890-A-RE2
        - MC Lyte - Cold rock a party, 1996; SR-17905; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17906. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED-6010; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6010-A-1
        - MC Lyte - Cold rock a party, 1996; SR-17906; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17905. 2 copies.
        - MC Lyte - Ice cream dream, 1992; SR-17907; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          Catalog # 31458 7412 1; A-side Matrix # 3148 7412 1A SP-3
          Perspective Records
        - MC Lyte - Bad as I wanna be, 1996; SR-17908; MC Lyte (Box 352)
          Catalog # ED-5881; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5881-A-1
        - MC Lyte - T.R.G. (The rap game) | One for the cuties, 1996; SR-17909; MC Lyte; Yo-Yo (Box 352)
          Catalog # ED-5878; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5878-A-1
        - MC Lyte - T.R.G. (The rap game) | One for the cuties, 1996; SR-17910; MC Lyte; Yo-Yo (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17911. 2 copies.
        - MC Lyte - T.R.G. (The rap game) | One for the cuties, 1996; SR-17911; MC Lyte; Yo-Yo (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17910. 2 copies.
        - MC Malika Love - She's bad, 1988; SR-17912; MC Malika Love (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17913. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # FMS62323; A-side Matrix # FMS-62323 A
        - Strickly Bizness - Non-stop rockin', 1987; SR-17913; Strickly Bizness (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17912. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # RFH-71157; A-side Matrix # RFH-1201
          RFH Records
        - MC Marcinho & Richa - Ensaio da portela | Vamos puxar o bonde, 1995; SR-17914; MC Marcinho & Richa; Big Rap (Box 352)
          Catalog # 443.083; A-side Matrix # 443083 A
        - MC Marcinho - Back to black, 1995; SR-17915; MC Marcinho (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17916. Different discs.
          Catalog # 443.046; A-side Matrix # 443046 A
        - MC Marcinho - Casual, a mais balancante do Rio, 1995; SR-17916; MC Marcinho (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17915. Different discs.
          Catalog # 443.063; A-side Matrix # 443063 A
        - MC Marcinho - Casual, a mais balancante do Rio, 1995; SR-17917; MC Marcinho (Box 352)
          Catalog # 443.066; A-side Matrix # 443066 A
        - MC Marcinho - Samba rap, 1995; SR-17918; MC Marcinho (Box 352)
        - MC Markynhos - Mania de dancar, 1995; SR-17919; MC Markynhos (Box 352)
          Catalog # 443.077; A-side Matrix # 443077 A
        - MC Markynhos - Mania de dancar, 1995; SR-17920; MC Markynhos (Box 352)
          Catalog # 443.075; A-side Matrix # 443075 A
        - MC Markynhos - Mania de dancar, 1995; SR-17921; MC Markynhos (Box 352)
        - MC Mars - Narcistic records, 1989; SR-17922; MC Mars (Box 352)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MC MARS 753 A1
        - MC Martay - Beyong control; Female force, 1989; SR-17923; MC Martay; D.J. D.B.M. (Box 352)
          Catalog # GTI 006T; A-side Matrix # KMA-03-AA1
          GTI Records
        - MC Mell'O' - The first chronicles of D.E.T.T., 1994; SR-17924; MC Mell'O' (Box 352)
          Catalog # 74321208511; A-side Matrix # 74321208511 A-1-1
          Natural Response
        - MC Nas-D - Girlz wit all da booty, 1995; SR-17925; MC Nas-D (Box 352)
          Catalog # PD-112; A-side Matrix # PD-112 RE-1
        - MC Nikke - Rap-n-scratch goes rambo, 1988; SR-17926; MC Nikke; DJ Rap-N-Scratch (Box 352)
          Catalog # SJR 201; A-side Matrix # SJR-201A
          Show Jazz Records Inc
          New Jersey
        - MC Ren - Keep it real, 1996; SR-17927; MC Ren (Box 352)
          Catalog # 88561-6339-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-6339-1A
          Ruthless Records
        - MC Ren - Ruthless for life, 1998; SR-17928; MC Ren (Box 352)
          Catalog # EAS 41097; A-side Matrix # XSS-41097-A-1B
        - MC Rene - Ein album namens bernd (disc one), 2000; SR-17929; MC Rene (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17930. Double album.
          Catalog # ST 33; A-side Matrix # B035284-01 A1 HL
          BMG Ariola Media GmbH
        - MC Rene - Ein album namens bernd (disc two), 2000; SR-17930; MC Rene (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17929. Double album.
          Catalog # ST 33; A-side Matrix # B035284-02 C1 HL
        - MC Serch - Daze in a weak, 1992; SR-17931; MC Serch (Box 352)
          Catalog # OAS 5084; A-side Matrix # XSS-05084-A-1A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - MC Sergio - Making a killin', 1989; SR-17932; MC Sergio (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17933. 2 copies.
          Catalog # WAR 2711; A-side Matrix # WAR 2711-TONY-H2
          Idlers
        - MC Sergio - Making a killin', 1989; SR-17933; MC Sergio (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17932. 2 copies.
        - MC Sergio - In the name of love, 1989; SR-17934; MC Sergio (Box 352)
          Catalog # WAR 039; A-side Matrix # WAR-039-O2
        - MC Shan - It don't mean a thing, 1990; SR-17935; MC Shan (Box 352)
          Catalog # 0-21501; A-side Matrix # 0-21501-A-SR1
          Cold Chillin'
        - MC Shan - The best of cold chillin' (disc one), 2001; SR-17936; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17937; SR-17938. Triple album.
          Catalog # LSR 8805; A-side Matrix # LSR-8805A
        - MC Shan - The best of cold chillin' (disc two), 2001; SR-17937; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17936; SR-17938. Triple album.
          Catalog # LSR 8805; A-side Matrix # LSR-8805C
        - MC Shan - The best of cold chillin' (disc three), 2001; SR-17938; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17936; SR-17937. Triple album.
          Catalog # LSR 8805; A-side Matrix # LSR-8805E
        - MC Shan - It don't mean a thing (remix), 1990; SR-17939; MC Shan (Box 352)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4306; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-4306-SR1
        - MC Shan - Juice crew law; They used to do it out in the park, 1988; SR-17940; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17941. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-21159; A-side Matrix # 0-21159-A-SR1
        - MC Shan - Born to be wild, 1988; SR-17941; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17940. Different discs.
          Catalog # 1-25797; A-side Matrix # B-32821-SH2
        - MC Shan - A mind is a terrible thing to waste, 1988; SR-17942; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17943. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-A-3222; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-3222-SH1
        - MC Shan - A mind is a terrible thing to waste, 1988; SR-17943; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17942. 2 copies.
        - MC Shan - I pioneered this, 1988; SR-17944; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17945. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-A-3318; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-3318-RE1-SH1
        - MC Shan - I pioneered this, 1988; SR-17945; MC Shan (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17944. 2 copies.
        - MC Shy D - I've gotta be tough, 1986; SR-17946; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          Catalog # GR-104; A-side Matrix # GR-104-A2
          Luke Skywalker Records
        - MC Shy D - Rapp will never die, 1985; SR-17947; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17948. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 3-85-FS-8; A-side Matrix # 3-85-FS-8-A
        - MC Shy D - Rapp will never die, 1985; SR-17948; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17947. 2 copies.
        - MC Shy D - Rapp will never die, 1985; SR-17949; MC Shy D (Box 352)
        - MC Shy D - Rapp will never die, 1985; SR-17950; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17951. 2 copies.
        - MC Shy D - Rapp will never die, 1985; SR-17951; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17950. 2 copies.
        - MC Shy D - Don't sweat me, 1990; SR-17952; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17953; SR-17954. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 8007; A-side Matrix # ON TOP-8007-A
          Benz Records
        - MC Shy D - Don't sweat me, 1990; SR-17953; MC Shy D (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17952; SR-17954. 2 copies.
        - En Vogue - Hold on, 1990; SR-17954; En Vogue (Box 352)
          In same jacket as # SR-17952; SR-17953. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-86234; A-side Matrix # STDM-58148-1